On the unstable SMP, there once was a team called the Invisible Mafia.
[Parrot] 在不稳定SMP里，曾有个叫隐形黑帮的队伍。
[Parrot] 在AshSwag带领下，黑帮铁律只有一条：保持隐身。
Led by the player AshSwag, the Mafia had one rule: Stay invisible,
[Parrot] 无论如何。
no matter what.
[Parrot] 你看，每个加入黑手党的人都被迫往滞束舱里扔一颗末影珍珠，
You see, whenever someone joined the Mafia, they were forced to throw an enderpearl into a stasis chamber,
[Parrot] 一旦身份暴露，他们就会被传送处决。
and if that player's identity was ever revealed, they would be teleported and killed.
[Parrot] 靠着这种邪恶手段，黑手党扩张到数千成员，
Through this evil method of control, the Mafia grew to thousands of members,
[Parrot] 接连征服各个文明。
and conquered civilization.
[Parrot] 一个接一个。
After civilization, after civilization.
[Parrot] 但就在服务器即将失去希望时，
But just as it seemed like the server had lost all hope,
[Parrot] 一小队玩家反击了，他们摧毁了黑手党的末影珍珠，拯救了服务器。
a small alliance of players fought back and saved the server by destroying the mafia's ender pearls.
[Parrot] 但为时已晚。
But it was already too late.
[Parrot] 由于黑手党的贪婪，世界大部分资源已被洗劫一空，
Due to the mafia's greed, most of the world's resources had been looted,
[Parrot] 自那时起，玩家们便陷入了无休止的生存斗争。
and since then, players have been in a constant struggle for survival.
[Parrot] 但有传言说，这些资源其实并未被销毁。
However, rumor has it that these resources were never destroyed.
[Parrot] 而是被藏在了某个不稳定的SMP世界里，一个叫做黑手党之墓的地方。
Instead, they were hidden somewhere out on the unstable SMP, in a place called the Tomb of the Mafia.
[Parrot] 我和朋友Theo弄到一本书，
Recently, my friend Theo and I got our hands on a book,
[Parrot] 最近，书上说墓穴位于末地维度遥远的一组坐标处。
which claimed that the tomb was located at a set of coordinates far out in the End dimension.
[Parrot] 但，坐标并非书中唯一的线索。
But, coordinates weren't the only thing written in this book.
[Parrot] 无论如何，千万要小心她。
Whatever you do, just be careful of her.
[Parrot] 我觉得往这边走应该就行。
I think we should be able to just head this way.
[Parrot] 从这个末地折跃门走，应该没问题。
If we take this end gateway, we should be fine.
[Parrot] 于是我和Theo开始按书中的坐标出发，
So Theo and I started heading out to the coordinates in the book,
[Parrot] 搞不懂这消息什么意思。
unsure as to what that message could even mean.
[Parrot] 你在往哪儿扔？
Where are you throwing?
[Parrot] 啥？
What?
[Parrot] 等等，怎么回事？
Wait, what?
[Theo] 没事，我直接用鞘翅就行。
Well, I can just use my elytra.
[Parrot] 好。
Okay.
[Parrot] 噢，我这样就行。
Oh, I can just do this.
[Parrot] 我的天。
Oh, my God.
[Parrot] 兄弟，兄弟。
Dude, dude.
[Theo] 行。
Okay.
[Parrot] 你没事吧。
Are you.
[Theo] 你还好吗？
Are you good?
[Parrot] 我直接掉进虚空了。
I just got dropped straight into the void.
[Theo] 你没事吧？
Are you okay?
[Parrot] 嗯，没事。
Yeah, I'm fine.
[Parrot] 我很好。
I'm fine.
[Parrot] 没问题。
[Parrot] 真没事。
I'm fine.
[Theo] 真险啊兄弟。
What a clutch, bro.
[Theo] 这都能救回来，你真是战神。
You're actually the goat for hitting that.
[Parrot] 天啊。
Oh, my gosh.
[Parrot] 我。
I.
[Parrot] 兄弟。
Dude.
[Parrot] 好了快走快走快走。
Okay, let's go, let's go, let's go.
[Parrot] 哇。
Wow.
[Parrot] 这个不稳定SMP的末地太危险了。
The end is dangerous on the unstable SMP.
[Parrot] 虽然末地维度看起来完好无损，但黑帮已经把这儿洗劫一空了。
Although the end Dimension looks untouched, the mafia has already looted everything here.
[Parrot] 离谱，都跑到25万格开外了，末地船还是
Dude, 250000 blocks out, and the end ships are.
[Parrot] 全被搜刮过了。
Still looted.
[Parrot] 就是说服务器里所有的鞘翅和潜影盒估计也都在墓里。
Meaning that pretty much all the server's elytras or shulker boxes are probably in the tomb as well.
[Parrot] 但想找到墓室，
But if we were going to even find the tomb in the first place,
[Parrot] 我们还得走更远，去末地几乎没人探索过的区域。
we would have to travel a lot further out than this, into an area of the End that has practically never been explored.
[Parrot] 前面应该有意思了。
I think we're about to see something interesting.
[Parrot] 我们到第一道末地环了。
I think that we've reached the first end ring.
[Theo] 那是啥？
What's that?
[Theo] 末地环是什么？
What's an end ring?
[Parrot] 把末地缩到最小看，
If you zoom out a ton in the End dimension, these end islands just cut off,
[Parrot] 外岛群到这儿突然截断，外面全是虚空环带。
and there's rings of void.
[Theo] 哇。
Whoa.
[Parrot] 也就是说，如果黑手党墓穴真的在这儿，
This means that if the tomb of the mafia is actually out here,
[Parrot] 那它完全就是在虚空中。
it's purely in the void.
[Parrot] 周围啥也没有。
There's nothing else.
[Theo] 真希望我们有两件鞘翅。
I really wish we had two elytras.
[Parrot] 我也希望，但没有啊。
Me too, but we don't, so.
[Parrot] Okey，准备好了吗？
Okay, you ready?
[Theo] 好了。
Yep.
[Parrot] 行，行。
Okay, okay.
[Theo] 出发了。
We're off.
[Parrot] 哥们，这完全是进虚空了啊。
Dude, into just pure void, bro.
[Theo] 记住了，千万别按潜行键。
All right, do not hit your shift key.
[Parrot] 知道，哥们。
I know, dude.
[Parrot] 我手都没碰键盘。
I'm not even touching my keyboard right now.
[Theo] 我都没碰键盘 兄弟，这也太吓人了。
I'm not even touching my keyboard Dude, this is terrifying.
[Theo] 不过最好这趟值得。
I I it's better be worth it, though.
[Theo] 我们最好能找到玛弗尔的宝藏古墓。
If We'd better get to the tomb of the mafer riches.
[Parrot] 会找到的。
We'll find it.
[Theo] 搞什么鬼 停停停 别停了快停下。
What in me ra stop, stopp Top stop sp stop.
[Parrot] 快停下。
So sto.
[Theo] 是我的。
It's my.
[Parrot] 你这样会害死自己。
I'm trying to get you're killed.
[Theo] 你反应过度了。
You're overreacting.
[Theo] 你太大惊小怪了。
[Parrot] 最终，在虚空中穿行数小时后，
And eventually, after traveling in complete void for hours,
[Parrot] 我和Theo按书里的坐标到了这儿，完全不知道会发现什么。
Theo and I arrived at the coordinates written in the book, completely unsure as to what we were going to find there.
[Parrot] 无论如何，千万要提防她。
Whatever you do, just be careful of her.
[Theo] 啥？
What?
[Parrot] 哟，看见没？
Yo, you see that?
[Theo] 搞什么鬼？
What the heck?
[Parrot] 应该就是这儿了。
I think this is it.
[Theo] 哥们，后面还有呢。
Dude, there's still more.
[Theo] 看这规模。
Look how big it is.
[Parrot] 是啊，真大。
Yeah, it's huge.
[Theo] 你觉得宝藏会长啥样？
What do you think the treasure is, like, gonna look like?
[Theo] 会不会就在个房子里之类的？
Do you think it's just gonna be in a house or something?
[Parrot] 不知道。
I don't know.
[Parrot] 不可能这么简单。
There's no way it's this easy.
[Theo] 到了。
Here we are.
[Parrot] 前面好像有条小路。
Looks like there's some sort of path in front of us.
[Theo] 不，它在毁树。
No, it's destroying the tree.
[Parrot] 没事。
It's fine.
[Parrot] 就放这儿吧。
Let's keep it up here.
[Parrot] 藏这儿挺合适，懂吗？
It's a nice hiding spot, okay?
[Parrot] 这地方感觉不太对劲。
Something feels off about this place.
[Parrot] 真没骗你。
I can't even lie.
[Theo] 不知道啊，兄弟。
I don't know, bro.
[Parrot] 无论如何，千万当心她。 就算死在这儿，至少也算...
Whatever you do, just be careful of her.
[Theo] 找了个不错的坟地。
Well, if we die here, at least it'll be a.
[Theo] 我们死不了。
A pretty spot for our graves.
[Parrot] 有扇门。
We're not gonna die.
[Parrot] 等等，什么？
There's a door.
[Theo] 后面有扇门。
Wait, what?
[Parrot] 哦，看见了。
There's a door back there.
[Theo] 看到了。
Oh, I see.
[Theo] 哇。
See it.
[Theo] 嗯。
Whoa.
[Parrot] 等等。
Yeah.
[Theo] 是这儿吗？
Wait.
[Parrot] 这就是黑手党墓穴？
Is this it?
[Parrot] 稍等。
Is this the tomb of the mafia?
[Theo] 你们...
Wait.
[Theo] 我...
Do you.
I'm.
[Theo] 我打算飞一圈看看有没有人。
I'm gonna, like, fly around and see if I can see anyone.
[Parrot] Theo在周围飞行时，我决定搜查这片区域。
While Theo flew around,
[Parrot] 不仅有扇巨型门，
I decided to investigate the area.
[Parrot] 还有两个漏斗——
And not only was there a massive door, but there were also two Hoppers,
[Parrot] 看来需要某种钥匙才能进入。
meaning that we probably needed some sort of key to enter.
[Parrot] Theo，看到人了吗？
Theo, see anyone?
[Theo] 目前看来风平浪静，兄弟。
And I mean, coast looks clear, bro.
[Parrot] 依我看，我们需要钥匙才能打开这扇门。
From what I can tell, we need some sort of key to enter this door.
[Parrot] 什么？
What?
[Theo] 我们干嘛不直接挖？
Why don't we just mine it?
[Parrot] 不行，我们不能这么干。
No, we shouldn't do that.
[Theo] 什么意思？
What do you mean?
[Theo] 为啥不行？
Why not?
[Parrot] 要是其他玩家知道这扇门，知道这座墓穴，但没人找到过它，
If other players know about this door, about this tomb, but nobody has found it,
[Parrot] 肯定有人试过挖穿这里吧？
I'm sure other players have probably already tried to mine through it,
[Parrot]是不？
right?
[Theo] 你觉得呢？
What do you think?
[Theo] 会不会有TNT陷阱之类的？
There's, like, a TNT trap here or something, or.
[Theo] 啥情况？
What?
[Parrot] 可能是警报，也可能是陷阱，说不准。
Maybe an alarm, maybe a trap,
[Parrot] 说不准。
I'm not sure.
[Theo] 要不...
I mean...
[Theo] 我们从顶上挖过去？
We could dig through the top.
[Parrot] 玩家，玩家，玩家，有玩家过来了。
Players, players, players, players coming.
[Parrot] Theo？
Theo?
[Parrot] Theo！
Theo!
[Parrot] Theo，有玩家！
Theo, there's players!
[Parrot] 快过来，躲好！
Come over here, hide!
[Parrot] 啥？
What?
[Theo] 在哪儿？
Where?
[Parrot] 哪儿？
[Parrot] 他们开着飞行器来了。
Coming on flying machines.
[Parrot] 看见没？
You see them?
[Theo] 看见了。
Yeah, I see them.
[Parrot] 躲这块石头后面。
Hide behind this rock.
[Theo] 怎么人尽皆知啊？
How does everybody know about this, bro?
[Parrot] 就是，太离谱了。
That's what I'm saying, it doesn't make any sense.
[Parrot] 先看看他们要干嘛。
Here, let's see what they do.
[Parrot] 但这帮人可不简单。
However, these were no ordinary players.
[Parrot] 没想到领头的是CoinMonkey，大家都叫他Coin。
To my surprise, one of them was CoinMonkey, or Coin for short.
[Parrot] 这哥们我几个月没见了，看这架势，
One of my friends that I hadn't seen in months, and from what it looked like,
[Parrot] 他和其他人正想办法闯过这道门。
he, as well as the other players, were trying to get past this door as well.
[Parrot] 快点。
Fast, bro.
[CoinMonke] 砸开它。
Come on, break it.
[CoinMonke] 等等等等。
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[CoinMonke] 硬闯不太好吧？
I don't know if we should break in.
[CoinMonke] 让我来。
I'll be.
[Parrot] 不然我们来干嘛？
What do you think we came here to do, bro?
[Theo] 可是...
This is.
[Theo] 行吧。
Yeah, I get that.
[CoinMonke] 懂了。
I get that.
[CoinMonke] 可要是，呃，有陷阱啥的呢？
But what if, like, there's, like, a trap or something?
[CoinMonke]  你看啊，万一，呃，咱们把门砸开，然后，呃，
You know, like, what if, like, we break the door and, like,
[CoinMonke]里头是数控陷阱？
there's, like, CNC trap?
[CoinMonke] 要是有钥匙之类的呢？
What if there's, like, a key or something?
[Parrot] 你知不知道黑手党藏了多少财宝啊？
Do you have any idea how much loot the mafia had, bro?
[CoinMonke]  懂你意思，不过，呃，
Yeah, I get that, but, like,
[CoinMonke]我明白。
I get.
[CoinMonke] 行吧行吧。
Okay, okay.
[CoinMonke] 你说得对。
You know, you're right.
[Parrot] 你说得对。
You're right.
[Parrot] 这样，要是你怕，
Okay, if you're scared,
[Parrot] 我来砸门。
I'll break it, bro.
[CoinMonke] 别别别，老大您请便。
No, no, no, you're good, boss.
[Parrot] 好，动手。
All right, let's go.
[Parrot] 搞什么——
What the.
[CoinMonke] 喂喂，你没事吧？
Yo, yo, you good?
[Parrot] 嗯。
Yeah.
[Parrot] 怎么回事？
What?
[Parrot] 我怎么瞎了？
Why am I blind, bro?
[Parrot] 等等，啥情况？
Wait, what?
[Parrot] 你在哪儿？
Where are you?
[Parrot] 有人吗？
Hello?
[CoinMonke] 啊，你说得对。
Oh, you're right.
[Parrot] 哦，我在这儿。
Oh, I'm here.
[Parrot] 不是，等等，这怎么回事？
I mean, wait, what's happening, bro?
[Parrot] 为啥咱俩都瞎了？
Why are we blind?
[CoinMonke] 我们怎么瞎了？
[Parrot] 啥？
What?
[CoinMonke] 搞什么。
What the.
[Theo] 等等，怎么回事？
Wait, what?
[Theo] 那是谁？
Who is that?
[Parrot] 这谁啊兄弟？
Who is this, bro?
[Parrot] 喂，这是我们队的人。
Yo, this is our team, bro.
[Theo] 有人吗？
Hello?
[Parrot] 在呢。
Yeah.
[CoinMonke] 你怎么知道的？
How did you know that, right?
[Theo] 我不知道。
I don't know.
[Parrot] 我不清楚。
I don't.
[Theo] 我不知道。
I don't know.
[CoinMonke] 我觉得我们不该这么干。
I don't think we should really do that.
[Parrot] 兄弟你想想。
Okay, think about it, bro.
[Parrot] 我们可以...
I like we could.
[Parrot] 我们四个人。
This is four of us.
[Parrot] 他们穿着带眼纹胸甲还在那晃悠。
They have an eye trim chest plate and fooling out.
[Parrot] 来吧。
Come on.
[Parrot] 硬币。
Coin.
[Theo] 我们...
We.
[Parrot] 我们要干掉他们。
We're gonna kill them, bro.
[Parrot] 离开。
Leave.
[Parrot] 对。
Yeah.
[Parrot] 不离开就别怪我们动手了。
Okay, if you don't leave, we're just gonna kill you, bro.
[Theo] 这到底是谁？
Who is this?
[Theo] 好了好了，我们得走了。
Okay, okay, we need to go.
[CoinMonke]
I don't, I don't like,
[CoinMonke] 我不...我不喜欢，这感觉不对劲。
I don't like the feeling of this.
[CoinMonke] 我们该不该这样干啊。
I don't know if we should do this or not.
[CoinMonke] 哇 哇 哇 哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[Parrot] 又越线了
Overline again.
[Parrot] 直接干掉他们
Just kill them.
[Parrot] 对 直接干掉 兄弟
Yeah, just kill them, bro.
[Theo] 直接杀
Just kill.
[Parrot] 喂 我听见了
Yo, I hear.
[Theo] 收起来
Put it away.
[Parrot] 等等 啥？
Wait, what?
[Theo] 蓝队？
Blue?
[Parrot] 估计我吓到他了
I guess I scared him.
[Parrot] 噢 喂 喂 得走了
Oh, yo, yo, we need to go.
[Theo] 搞什么 搞什么？
What the, what the?
[Parrot] P 再不帮忙他们就要死了
P, they're going to die if they don't help them.
[Theo] 到底救不救？
Arere receiving them or not then?
[Theo] 不用合作吗？
you don have to collabro?
[CoinMonke] 天啊 行吧
Oh gosh, Ookay.
[Parrot] 必须帮忙
We have to help.
[Parrot] 硬币硬币硬币硬币 标准标准...标准这些...
Coin, coin, coin, coin Coin coin Standard standard th, standard these what the dode dode come over here Perce legent I I mean,
[Parrot] 搞什么 过来这边 Pearce legent 我是说 Pearce legent 他明明已经死了
Pearce legent He's literally dead.
[Parrot] 我的天
Oh my god.
[Theo] 兄弟们
Guys.
[Parrot] 喂
Yo.
[Parrot] 什么情况 那是谁？
What the, who is that?
[Parrot] 兄弟们 兄弟们 兄弟们
Guys, guys, guys.
[Parrot] 快走快走快走快走！
We gotta go, we gotta go, we gotta go, we gotta go.
[Parrot] 怎么办？
What do we do?
[Parrot] 这边这边。
This way, this way.
[Theo] 跑跑跑跑跑。
Run, run, run, run, run.
[Parrot] 有没有末影珍珠？
Do you have any, do you have any ender pearls?
[Parrot] 别管了直接跑！
Yo, just run, just run, just run.
[Theo] 跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑。
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
[Parrot] 快走快走快走快走！
Just go, just go, just go, just go, just go.
[Parrot] 快走！
Just go.
[Parrot] 跑跑跑跑跑跑跑跑。
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
[Theo] 你们没事吧？
You guys good?
[Parrot] 兄弟们冲啊！
Guys, go, go, go.
[Parrot] 你怎么会在这儿？
Why are you, why are you here?
[CoinMonke] 搞什么...
What the.
[Parrot] 好家伙
Okay, dude, that.
[Parrot] 那可是全世界最厉害的Minecraft玩家啊
That's literally the best Minecraft player in the entire world, bro.
[Parrot] 对啊
Yeah.
[Parrot] 啥情况？
What?
[Theo] 为什么？
Why?
[Theo] 她怎么会...
Why is she.
[Theo] 她来这儿干嘛？
What is she doing here?
[Parrot] 不知道
I don't know.
[Theo] 发生什么了？
What is happening?
[Parrot] 这就是Flame在书里提到的意思
That's what flame meant in the book.
[Parrot] 这墓是Marlo守着的，兄弟。
The tomb is guarded by Marlo, bro.
[Theo] 他该说清楚点的
He could have been a bit more specific, bro.
[Theo] 真是的
Like, come on.
[Parrot] 好 我们走
Okay, let's go.
[Parrot] 必须
We gotta.
[Parrot] 必须离开
We gotta get out.
[Parrot] 必须逃出去
[Theo] 那个 我们难道
Well, are we just.
[Theo] 要原路返回？
Are we just going back?
[Parrot] 不知道
I don't know.
[Parrot] 但我们必须离开这岛
We need to leave this island, though, dude.
[Parrot] 兄弟 快带我们走
Dude, get us out.
[CoinMonke] 天
Dad.
[CoinMonke] 哦 老天
Oh, my gosh.
[CoinMonke] 刚才那是什么？
Actually, what was that?
[Parrot] 要知道，在数亿《我的世界》玩家里，
You see, out of the hundreds of millions of people who play Minecraft,
[Parrot]  Marlo简直是顶尖高手，最近刚超越it's real me那帮人。
Marlo is literally the best player, recently surpassing the likes of it's real me to claim that title.
[Parrot] 连Marlo这种强者都守门，
And if someone as strong as Marlo was guarding that door,
[Parrot] 我真不知道该怎么进去。
I had no idea how we were supposed to get inside.
[Theo] 伙计，我。
Dude, I.
[Theo] 我不想扫大伙的兴。
I don't want to push you guys off.
[Parrot] Coin，这附近你熟吗？
Coin, do you know anywhere near here, dude?
[Parrot] 咱们已经没地方可去了。
Like we have nowhere to go.
[CoinMonke] 我还真知道。
I actually do.
[Theo] 我知道个地方。
I know a place.
[CoinMonke] 我知道个地方。
[Parrot] 行，行。
Okay, okay.
[Parrot] 把坐标告诉Theo，让他先过去。
Tell Theo the coordinates so he can just go there before.
[CoinMonke] 好，好，好。
Okay, okay, okay.
[Theo] 这也太乱了。
This is messed up, bro.
[CoinMonke] 没事，交给我。
All right, I got you.
[Theo] 我来处理。
I will.
[Parrot] 回头见。
Yo, see you later, bro.
[CoinMonke] 走了。
Bye.
[CoinMonke] 那人是谁？
Who is that guy?
[CoinMonke] 没在你队伍里见过。
I haven't seen him in your crew.
[Parrot] 那是我朋友。
That's my friend.
[CoinMonke] 刚才那是怎么回事？
What happened to like that?
[Theo] 知道吗？
You know what?
[CoinMonke] 我不多问了。
I won't ask any questions.
[Parrot] 所以你来这干嘛？
Okay so what were you doing out here dude?
[Parrot] 咱们好久没见了。
Like it's been like a while since we last talked.
[Parrot] 真没想到会在黑手党墓穴碰到你。
Um, but I didn't expect to meet you out here at the tomb of the mafia.
[CoinMonke] 我以为再也见不到你了。
I never thought I would see you ever again.
[CoinMonke] 我加入了强盗团伙，然后到了这儿，没想到会被那帮人伏击——
Yeah, no, basically all I did was just join a bandit crew and we just ended up here and I didn't expect for us to get jumped like that by whoever,
[CoinMonke] 那个Mar...他们叫什么来着？
Mar, how do you say their name?
[CoinMonke] Marlow？
Marlow?
[Parrot] Marlow。
Marlow.
[CoinMonke] 真不愿回想，太感谢你了，
I don't want to think about that man, thank you so much,
[CoinMonke] 说真的，要不是你在我就没命了。
genuinely, I don't know if I- if you weren't there I would have died.
[Parrot] 确实，Marlowe杀过的玩家少说上百，我们能活下来真是奇迹。
It was true, Marlowe had probably killed hundreds of players, and the fact that we were even alive right now was a miracle.
[Parrot] 但我不会因此放弃潜入墓穴的计划，
But, I wasn't going to let this stop me from breaking into the tomb,
[Parrot] 幸好Koin说了，我们要去的地方正好能解决这事。
and luckily, Koin explained that this place we were heading to would help me do just that.
[Parrot] 那到底是什么东西？
What in the world is that, dude?
[Parrot] 哦，是他们。
Oh, they.
[CoinMonke] 到了再解释。
I'll explain when we get there.
[Parrot] 等等，那是Theo吗？
Okay, wait, is that Theo?
[CoinMonke] 对，下面好像有个朋友。
Yeah, I think that's a friend down there.
[CoinMonke] 嗯，他在那儿。
Yeah, there he is.
[Parrot] Theo，最近怎么样？
Theo, what's good?
[Theo] 哟，你们这些慢吞吞的家伙总算到了。
Yo, about time you slow pokes made it over here.
[Theo] 可以啊兄弟。
All right, bro.
[Parrot] 我们花了一小时才到。
Took us an hour, bro.
[Parrot] 这末地主城太疯狂了，就建在末地环中间，
This is a crazy end base, and it's just in the middle of an end ring,
[Parrot] 完全被虚空包围。
like, completely surrounded by void.
[CoinMonke] 不管了，我直接冲了。
All right, well, I'm just gonna go for it.
[Theo] 嚯。
Oh.
[CoinMonke] 哦，好吧。
Oh, okay.
[CoinMonke] 其实这就是末地驿站。
All right, well, basically, this is the end station.
[CoinMonke] 老有人来这儿赌博，搞各种名堂。
You know, people go here all the time to gamble, do all that kind of stuff.
[CoinMonke] 说真的。
I cannot lie.
[CoinMonke] 提醒你们一下。
Fair warning.
[Parrot] 合理。
Fair.
[CoinMonke] 那玩意儿吸引你目光了吧？
Yeah, no, that got your eye, huh?
[CoinMonke] 但有个问题，唯一的问题就是，
But the one bad thing about this, the one bad thing about this,
[CoinMonke] 这儿怪人特别多。
there's a lot of strange people here, man.
[CoinMonke] 不骗你们。
I'm not gonna lie to you.
[Parrot] 什么叫怪人？
What do you mean, strange people?
[Theo] 走。
Let.
[CoinMonke] 对，直接
Yeah, let's just.
[CoinMonke] 直接进去吧
Let's just go inside.
[CoinMonke] 先提醒你们
I'm warning you guys, by the way.
[Parrot] 嗯
Yeah.
[CoinMonke] 里面长这样
Here's the inside.
[Parrot] 这啥
What the.
[Theo] 没错
Yeah.
[Theo] 嘿，你看什么呢？
Hey, what are you looking at?
[Theo] 看什么呢？
What are you looking at?
[Theo] 专心打你的游戏。
Come back to your game, bro.
[Theo] 你作弊了。
I know you cheated, bro.
[Theo] 这不公平。
Bro, that's not fair, bro.
[Theo] 我知道你作弊了。
I know you cheated, bro.
[Rasplin] 你能拿我怎样？
What are you gonna do about it?
[Theo] 我不想动手。
I don't want to do this, bro.
[Theo] 把东西还回来。
Just give it back, bro.
[Theo] 喂。
Yo.
[CoinMonke] 怎么回事？
What's that?
[CoinMonke] 那人刚刚...
The guy just.
[CoinMonke] 好吧。
All right.
[CoinMonke] 明白我的意思了吧？
Well, yeah, you see what I mean, though, right?
[Parrot] 嗯。
Yeah.
[Parrot] 我们到底来这干嘛？
Dude, why are we even here?
[Parrot] 这对找古墓有帮助吗？
Is this gonna help us find the tomb at all?
[CoinMonke] 说真的，要听我劝吗？
Honestly, can I give you my honest advice?
[CoinMonke] 我的真心话...
My honest, like.
[CoinMonke] 就是我真正的建议？
Like my honest advice?
[CoinMonke] 我觉得你们不该回那里。
I I don't think you should really go back there, though.
[CoinMonke] 实话实说。
I can't lie.
[Parrot] 非去不可。
We have to.
[Theo] 好了，头儿发话了。
All right, you heard the boss.
[Theo] 必须去。
We have to.
[CoinMonke] 行吧，去找中间那个人聊聊。
All right, well, go talk to the guy in the middle.
[CoinMonke] 刚干掉Lord的那家伙，管他叫什么。
The guy who just killed Lord, whatever his name was.
[CoinMonke] 我就知道这么多。
But that's all I have to really say.
[Parrot] 行，回头见Coin。
All right, see a coin.
[Parrot] 碰见你真高兴兄弟。
It was nice running into you, bro.
[CoinMonke] 是啊。
Yeah, I know.
[Parrot] 太好了。
Great.
[CoinMonke] 遇到你真的很开心。
Really nice running into you.
[Parrot] 天呐。
Oh, my gosh.
[CoinMonke] 好了，你们继续。
All right, well, you guys have.
[Parrot] 你们俩。
You guys.
[CoinMonke] 祝你们旅途顺利。
Good luck on your journey.
[CoinMonke] 回头见各位。
All right, I'll see y'all later.
[CoinMonke] 再见。
Bye.
[Parrot] 好。
All right.
[CoinMonke] 保重。
Peace.
[Theo] 幸会。
Nice to meet you.
[CoinMonke] 我也很荣幸。
Nice to meet you, too, man.
[Parrot] 你好。
Hello.
[Rasplin] 你好啊。
Hello there.
[Parrot] 不知道你刚听到没，那个叫Coin的说他了解黑手党墓穴的事。
So I don't know if you overheard, but that guy, coin said he knew something about the Tomb of the Mafia.
[Rasplin]
Well,
[Rasplin] 这个嘛，
I do know things about the vault, but,
[Rasplin] 我确实知道些地牢的情报，但我现在更想玩这游戏。
I mean, I just want to play this game right now, so.
[Parrot] 游戏？
A game?
[Parrot] 我都走到这儿了怎么可能回头。
I hadn't come this far just to turn around now.
[Parrot] 要了解古墓还得先玩个游戏，
And if I had to play some game to learn more about the Tomb,
[Parrot] 那就这样吧。
so be it.
[Parrot] 我别无选择。
I didn't have a choice.
[Parrot] 这是什么？
What's this?
[Rasplin] 潜影盒？
A shulker box?
[Parrot] 听着，若要我坐下来陪你玩这游戏，
Oh, if I'm gonna sit down here and play this game with you,
[Parrot] 你得证明自己了解古墓的事。
I need proof that you know something about the Tomb.
[Rasplin] 呵，
Well,
[Rasplin] 古墓钥匙此刻就在我手中。
I have the key to the tomb right here in my hands.
[Parrot] 等等，你从哪弄到的钥匙？
Wait, where did you get that key from?
[Rasplin] 从Marlow那儿偷来的。
I stole it from Marlow.
[Theo] 老兄，他八成在撒谎。
Dude, he's probably lying, bro.
[Theo] 你会上当的。
You're gonna get scammed.
[Parrot] 怎么玩？
How do we play?
[Rasplin] 好，兄弟，这叫八重试炼。
Okay, bro, this is a game called eightfold.
[Rasplin] 规则很简单。
The rules are really simple.
[Rasplin] 首先你会拿到一件物品。
First, you will be given an item.
[Rasplin] 别让任何人看见。
Don't show anybody this item.
[Parrot] 行。
Okay.
[Rasplin] 墙上写着每件物品的分数。
As you can see on the wall, that item has a point value.
[Rasplin] 根据你物品的分数下注。
Based on the point value of the item you get, you can make a bet.
[Rasplin] 想继续玩就得投入和我一样或更多的钻石。
If you want to keep playing, you have to put in the same amount of diamonds or more than me.
[Rasplin] 或者你也可以随时弃牌，这样箱子里的东西就全归我。
Or at any point, you can fold, which means I keep everything in the chest.
[HerobaneNair] Raspun押了一张床和32颗钻石，你跟注还是弃牌？
Raspun is bed, 32 diamonds, would you like to match or fold?
[Parrot] 根据墙上的规则，泥土方块显然是最差的道具，
Based on what was on the wall, a dirt block was apparently the worst item,
[Parrot] 分值只有1点。
with a point value of one.
[Parrot] 但32颗钻石还算不赖，反正这局只是热身赛。
But 32 diamonds wasn't too bad, and this was still only a warm up anyway.
[Parrot] 我跟注。
I'll match.
[Rasplin] 现在你将获得第二件道具。
Now, you're gonna get a second item.
[Rasplin] 开始最后一轮下注。
Now for the final round of betting.
[HerobaneNair] Raspyn加注了一组钻石。
Raspyn has added to his bet one stack of diamonds.
[HerobaneNair] 你跟注还是弃牌？
Would you like to match or fold?
[Parrot] 我只有绿宝石和泥土方块，总分才七点，
Since I had only an emerald and a dirt block, my total point value was seven,
[Parrot] 显然处于劣势。
which was definitely on the weaker side.
[Parrot] 继续玩下去不太明智。
Staying in this game didn't make much sense.
[Parrot] 我弃牌。
I fold.
[Parrot] 果然，Raspyn的手牌是八点，而我只有七点。
And sure enough, Raspyn's hand was worth eight points, while mine was only worth seven.
[Parrot] 这局你赢了，不过这不只是概率游戏。
I see you won, but this isn't just a game about pure odds.
[Parrot] 你刚才可能是在诈唬，想故意吓退我。
You could have been lying right there, like bluffing, to try to get me to fold on purpose.
[Parrot] 没错。
Well, exactly.
[Rasplin] 所以这游戏才有趣啊。
That's what makes this game so fun.
[Rasplin] 现在准备好认真玩了吗？
So are you ready to actually play now?
[Theo] 嗯，
Yeah,
[Theo] 行吧。
I think.
[Theo] 这轮跟注就行了对吧？
I think it's good to call it there, right?
[Parrot] 开始吧。
Let's do it.
[Theo] 好嘞。
Okay, dude.
[Theo] 我呢
Well, I.
[Theo] 嗯
Yep.
[Theo] 别听Theo瞎扯
Don't listen to Theo bald.
[Theo] 对
Yep.
[Theo] 不管Theobald说什么都是在胡诌
Nope, just whatever Theobald's saying is probably just a bunch of yep.
[Parrot] 但Theo说得确实有道理
Theo did have a point.
[Parrot] 我本来很可能空手而归
There was a chance that I was going to walk away from this completely empty-handed.
[Parrot] 但看到首件物品是下界合金锭——
But seeing that my first item was a netherite ingot, which had the highest point value in the whole game,
[Parrot] 全场最高分值的物品，我知道必须继续
I knew that I had to keep going.
[Parrot] 尤其当策略得当的话，
Especially since if I played my cards right,
[Parrot] 我还能拿到古墓钥匙
I could get the key to the tomb.
[HerobaneNair] 最后一位下注七块下界合金锭。
Last one has bet seven netherite ingots.
[HerobaneNair] 跟注还是弃牌？
Would you like to match or fold?
[Parrot] 什么？
What?
[Rasplin] 我们定一个下界合金锭等价32颗钻石。
We'll say one netherite ingot is 32 diamonds.
[Parrot] 我跟注。
I match.
[Theo] 这太浪费了兄弟。
This is such a waste, dude.
[Theo] 他只是给你看了张纸，你现在却要押上全部身家。
He literally just showed you a piece of paper, and now you're putting all of this on the line.
[Parrot] 可惜我第二件物品是个草方块。
Unfortunately, my second item was a dirt block.
[Parrot] 但毕竟总点数是九点，值得继续跟注。
But still, since I had a total point value of nine, it made sense to stay in.
[HerobaneNair] Russell加注九个下界合金锭。
Russell has been Nine netherite ingots.
[Parrot] 再加九个？
An additional nine?
[HerobaneNair] 对。
Yes.
[Theo] 天啊。
Oh my god.
[Parrot] 什么？
What?
[Parrot] 我又输了。
I lost again.
[Theo] Parrot，我们到底在干嘛？
Parrot, like, what are we doing here, bro?
[Rasplin] 这就是游戏规则，朋友。
That's just the game, my friend.
[Parrot] 我的物品快速消耗，但幸运的是这次又拿到了
I was running out of items fast, but luckily, once again,
[Parrot] 下界合金锭——最高点数八点。
I was given a netherite ingot, worth the maximum of eight points.
[HerobaneNair] RaspLyn加注一组钻石。
RaspLyn has bet one stack of diamonds.
[HerobaneNair] 跟注还是弃牌？
Would you like to match or fold?
[Parrot] 如果RaspLyn只押一摞钻石，按理说他的东西应该比我的差。
If RaspLyn was only betting one stack of diamonds, logically he probably had a worse item than me.
[Parrot] 我跟。
I'll match it.
[Parrot] 一颗绿宝石。
An emerald.
[Parrot] 加上我之前的下界合金锭，
Paired with my netherite ingot from before,
[Parrot] 我现在有14点。
I now had a point value of 14.
[Parrot]
Statistically, Rasplin had around a 3.5%
[Parrot] 按概率算，Rasplin的手牌比我好的几率只有3.5%。
chance of having a better hand than me.
[Parrot] 这局基本稳赢。
Winning this was pretty much guaranteed.
[Rasplin] 好，Parrot，我要你押上全部家当。
Alright, Parrot, I want you to bet everything that you own.
[Rasplin] 你穿的盔甲、不死图腾、所有东西，那个潜影盒里的全部押上来。
The armor you're wearing, your totems, whatever you have, the shulker I want you to put everything on the line right now.
[Rasplin] 作为交换，我会给你想要的东西。
And in exchange, I will give you the thing that you want.
[Rasplin] 密室钥匙。
The key to the vault.
[Theo] 这不过就是张纸。
It is literally just a piece of paper.
[Theo] 他用三个糖合的。
He crafted that with three sugar.
[HerobaneNair] 直接全押了。
Is going all in.
[HerobaneNair] 你跟注还是弃牌？
Would you like to match or fold?
[Theo] 不可能，兄弟。
There's no way, dude.
[Theo] 绝对有诈。
There's.
[Theo] 他在唬人。
He is lying.
[Theo] 这局有黑幕。
The game is rigged.
[Parrot] 你才。
You are.
[Theo] 你搞什么啊老兄？
What are you doing, bro?
[HerobaneNair] 已跟注。
It has matched.
[Parrot] Rasplin手上有下界合金锭和钻石。
Rasplin had a netherite Ingot and a diamond.
[Parrot] 唯一能大过我的牌。
The only hand that was better than mine.
[Parrot] 啥？
What?
[Parrot] 搞什么。
What the.
[Parrot] 喂，兄弟。
Hey, yo, bro.
[Theo] 这是啥。
What is.
[Theo] 我的天。
Oh, my God.
[Theo] 鹦鹉。
Parrot.
[Theo] 穿上盔甲，鹦鹉。
Get your armor, parrot.
[Parrot] 怎么回事？
What's going on?
[Theo] 哦。
Oh.
[Parrot] 走起。
Let'S go.
[Parrot] 走。
Let's go.
[Parrot] 哥们。
Dude.
[Parrot] 这波打得真不错。
Okay, that was actually really good.
[Theo] 你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
[Theo] 比如？
Like what?
[Parrot] 啥？
What?
[Theo] 你这话什么意思。
What do you mean that.
[Theo] 这哪算好啊？
What do you mean that was good, dude?
[Theo] 你白扔了盔甲。
You just threw away your armor for nothing.
[Parrot] 那家伙从Marlo那儿偷了把钥匙。
Well, that guy stole a key off of Marlo.
[Parrot] 如果钥匙是假的，Marlo根本没理由出现在那个车站。
Marlo would have no reason to show up to that station if the key wasn't real.
[Theo] 那又能改变什么，鹦鹉？
And what does that change about our situation, parrot?
[Parrot] 我们就照那个玩家做的那样来。
We're gonna do exactly what that player did.
[Parrot] 我们要从Marlow那儿偷钥匙。
We're gonna steal the key from Marlow.
[Parrot] 怎么样？
Well?
[Theo] 你带路？
You gonna lead the way?
[Theo] 你还好吗？
You okay?
[Parrot] 这计划是我提的 但怎么说呢
I know this was my plan, but, like,
[Parrot] 从没遇到过这样的玩家。
I've never ran into a player like this.
[Theo] 对，就这个。
Yeah, this.
[Theo] 确实，老实说。
Yeah, I can't lie.
[Theo] 这家伙可比咱们之前对付的那些都吓人。
It's a little bit scarier than any other person we've tried to fight.
[Theo] 哥们，我——好吧，给你。
Dude, I- okay, here.
[Theo] 你用鞘翅吧，你都没穿护甲。
You should take the Elytra, 'cause you have no armor.
[Theo] 你肯定会被秒的。
Like, you're just gonna get one tapped.
[Theo] 哥们，咱还能回头。
Dude, we can still turn around.
[Theo] 想回头还来得及。
We can still turn around if you want.
[Theo] 现在还不晚。
Like, it's not too late.
[Theo] 你来决定。
It's your call, man.
[Parrot] 正常对决的话，我们根本打不过Marlow。
In a normal duel, if we were forced to fight Marlow, we wouldn't stand a chance.
[Parrot] 但关键是，我们只需拿到钥匙，
But the point is, if all we have to do is get the key,
[Parrot] 那就有机会了。
then we have a shot.
[Parrot] 我有个主意。
I think I have an idea.
[Parrot] 把盔甲穿上。
Put on your armor.
[Theo] 嗯。
Yeah.
[Parrot] 假设这里是墓道的漏斗区。
Pretend this is where the hoppers are of the tomb.
[Parrot] 把物品扔到它们身上。
Throw an item onto them.
[Parrot] 你懂我意思吧？
You see what I'm trying to get at?
[Parrot] 计划很简单。
The plan was simple.
[Parrot] 我提议把漏斗锁在墓门外面。
I was proposing that we lock the hoppers outside of the tomb door,
[Parrot] 然后Marlow想用她的钥匙进去时
and then, when Marlow tried to enter with her key,
[Parrot] 我直接用冲击二弓把她轰飞。
I'd shoot her away with my punch 2 bow.
[Parrot] 与此同时，
At the same time,
[Parrot] Theo会在Pearl反应过来前闯进去偷走钥匙。
Theo would enter Pearl in and steal the key before she could even react.
[Parrot] 但我们只有这一次机会。
But we only get one shot at this.
[Parrot] 她压根不知道咱们在岛上。
She doesn't even know we're on the island, dude.
[Theo] 好，你射中她后，她会转向你，对吧？
Okay, so after you shoot her, she's gonna turn to you, right?
[Theo] 对。
Yeah.
[Parrot] 好的。
Okay.
[Theo] 要是附近再挖条逃生通道呢？
What if we have, like, an escape tunnel nearby as well?
[Theo] 就像我用了末影珍珠之后。
So, like, after I Pearl.
[Parrot] 好，就这么办。
Yeah, let's do that.
[Parrot] 动手吧。
Let's do that.
[Theo] 说真的，这计划不算糟。
It's not even a terrible plan, honestly.
[Theo] 我觉得我们能搞定。
I think we can pull this off.
[Parrot] 我觉得我们能搞定。
I think we can pull it off, dude.
[Parrot] 但搞砸就全完了。
But if we mess it up, this is over.
[Parrot] 但Theo，你知道我还带了什么吗？
But, Theo, you know what I did also bring?
[Parrot] 啊？
What?
[Parrot] 箭矢小技巧。
Tip to arrows.
[Parrot] 我有迟缓之箭。
I have arrows of slowness.
[Theo] 对她用？
To use on her?
[Parrot] 嗯。
Yeah.
[Parrot] 噢，她来了。
Oh, she's here.
[Theo] 在哪儿？
Where?
[Parrot] 就在那儿。
Right there.
[Parrot] 对，就在下面。
Right, right down there.
[Parrot] 老兄，我从未见过如此无情的玩家。
Dude, I don't think I've ever seen a player so heartless, bro.
[Theo] 是啊，刚才那波。
Yeah, that was.
[Theo] 当着大伙儿的面把Rasp干掉，有点冷血啊。
That was kind of cold-blooded just killed rasp when in front of everyone,
[Theo] 哥们。
bro.
[Parrot] 她干掉了那四个玩家。
And she killed those four players.
[Theo] 进了逃生通道后往哪走？
Where do we go once we're in the escape tunnel?
[Parrot] 我们躲起来等时间过去，再回古墓。
We run and we hide, and we wait for enough time to pass and then we come back to the tomb.
[Theo] 好，要是走散了，我们在哪儿碰头？
Okay, if we get split off, where do we meet again?
[Parrot] 湖边碰头。
Meet by that lake.
[Parrot] 但执行这个计划谈何容易，要想成功，
But executing this plan was a lot easier said than done, and in order for it to even work,
[Parrot] 我们得先锁住漏斗，确保它们吸不进任何物品。
we would first need to lock the hoppers, making sure that they couldn't pick up any items.
[Parrot] 你。
You.
[Parrot] 要动手就趁现在。
If we're gonna do this, now is our chance.
[Parrot] 我没看见她。
I don't see her.
[Theo] 好的。
Okay.
[Parrot] 拉杆在哪儿？
Where are the levers?
[Theo] 放开我。
Let me go.
[Theo] 拿着。
Here, take.
[Theo] 好，当心点。
Okay, be careful.
[Theo] 快点儿。
Be fast.
[Parrot] 哦，糟了。
Oh, oh.
[Parrot] 虽然我们锁住了漏斗，但这还只是第一步。
Although we had managed to lock the hoppers, that was still only the easy part.
[Parrot] 从这里开始，我得等Marlow试图进墓才行，
From here, not only would I have to wait until Marlow tried to enter the tomb,
[Parrot] 但我的箭矢角度和时机必须分毫不差。
but the angle and timing of my arrow needed to be extremely precise.
[Parrot] 而且，
And on top of that,
[Parrot] 我把天大的信任都押在Theo身上了，毕竟偷钥匙的人是他。
I was putting an insane amount of trust into Theo, since he would be the one stealing the key itself.
[Theo] 你以为躲那儿我看不见？
Don't you know that I can see you hiding right there?
[Parrot] 我做到了。
I did.
[Parrot] 我放了。
[Parrot] 我做了。
I did.
[Parrot] 她来了。
She's here.
[Theo] 好，我走这边。
All right, I'm going this way.
[Theo] 我。
I'm.
[Parrot] 我。
[Theo] 我走了。
I'm leaving.
[Theo] 她盯上我了。
She's on me.
[Theo] 好，要是走散了我们去哪碰头？
Okay, if we get split off, where do we meet again?
[Parrot] 湖边碰头。
Meet by that lake.
[Theo] 你好。
Hello.
[Theo] 湖边见。
Meet by the lake.
[Parrot] 嗯。
Yeah.
[Parrot] 啥？
What?
[Theo] 在哪儿？
Where?
[Theo] 你在哪？
Where are you?
[Parrot] 我在这儿。
I'm over here.
[Parrot] 我在石头后面。
I'm over here behind the rock.
[Parrot] 好的。
Okay.
[Parrot] 你在哪？
Where are you?
[Theo] 我的天哪，哥们。
Oh, my God, dude.
[Theo] 我拿到了。
I I have it.
[Theo] 钥匙在我这。
I have the key.
[Theo] 我在丁香丛里。
I'm in the lilacs.
[Theo] 嗯，我在这儿。
Yeah, I'm right here.
[Parrot] 好，我们该撤了。
Okay, we should run.
[Parrot] 快撤。
We should run.
[Parrot] 哥们儿。
Dude.
[Theo] 我的天。
Oh my God.
[Parrot] 啥？
What?
[Theo] 钥匙到手了。
We have the key.
[Parrot] 这边，跟我来。
Here, come this way.
[Parrot] 得找个地方躲起来。
We gotta find a hiding spot.
[Theo] 嗯。
Yeah.
[Parrot] 我们只需等待足够时间流逝。
We just have to wait for enough time to pass by.
[Parrot] 等她忘了咱们或者离开岛，咱们就能溜进墓里了。
And when she forgets about us or just leaves the island, that's our chance to sneak into the tomb.
[Parrot] 就这儿。
Right here.
[Theo] 算你一个。
You're in this.
[Theo] 你也有份。
[Parrot] 知道啦。
I know, I know.
[Theo] 对，她肯定有备用钥匙。
Yeah, she must have, like, an extra key.
[Parrot] 这是啥
What is the.
[Parrot] 钥匙是啥？
What is the key?
[Parrot] 我能。
Can I.
[Parrot] 能让我看看吗？
Can I see what it is?
[Theo] 是啊，是啊，就是。
Yeah, yeah, it's.
[Theo] 在这在这在这。
It's here, here, here.
[Parrot] 嗯。
Yeah.
[Parrot] Qw7rz.
Qw7rz.
[Parrot] 哦，懂了。
Oh, I see.
[Parrot] 就是张带密码的纸。
So it's a piece of paper with a code.
[Theo] 老兄，你觉得这墓里能有啥？
Dude, we're like, what do you think is in the tomb, man?
[Parrot] 宝藏。
Treasure.
[Parrot] 哥们，那公会可是有上千号人的大团队。
Dude, the mafia was a team with thousands of players.
[Theo] 我懂，兄弟。
I know, dude.
[Parrot] 想想他们积攒了多少财富。
Think about how much wealth they amassed.
[Parrot] 他们都有几千套下界合金装备了。
They had literally thousands of netherite sets.
[Parrot] Theo，你不觉得Marlow守着这座坟墓很奇怪吗？
Theo, don't you think it's kind of strange that Marlow like guards this tomb?
[Parrot] 她技术超神，对吧？
Like she's extremely skilled, right?
[Parrot] 而且威力惊人。
And also powerful.
[Parrot] 嗯。
Yeah.
[Parrot] 我觉得她想做什么都能做成。
I feel like she could do whatever she wanted to do.
[Parrot] 她能统领万千玩家。
She could rule over thousands of players.
[Parrot] 她都能自立门户了。
She could start her own civilization.
[Parrot] 她可以当赏金猎人，义警，什么都行。
She could become a bounty hunter, a vigilante, anything.
[Parrot] 可她却守着末地深处五十万格外的一座无名陵墓。
But yet for some reason she's guarding this random tomb 500,000 blocks out in the end dimension.
[Theo] 我不确定。
I don't know man.
[Parrot] 蹲下啊兄弟。
Also crouch dude.
[Theo] 我的错。
Oh that's my bad.
[Theo] 我压根不想琢磨这事。
Like I can't even be asked to think about this bro.
[Theo] 我也不知道。
Like I don't know.
[Theo] 我看她就是故意蹲守这个宝藏，专挑过来寻宝的萌新下手。
I think she just gets a kick out of just camping this treasure that everyone's trying to get to and just to tapping all the noobs who come out here.
[Theo] 给。
Here.
[Parrot] 兄弟。
Bro.
[Theo] 据我所知，她就是纯粹的恶。
For all I know, she's just evil.
[Theo] 她就是为了这个。
She's just doing it for the.
[Theo] 图个乐子。
For the laughs.
[HerobaneNair] 我不。
I don't.
[Theo] 说不好。
I don't know.
[Theo] 我真不知道。
I literally don't know.
[Theo] 我也无所谓。
I don't really care either.
[Theo] 我只想要宝藏。
I just want the treasure.
[Theo] 我只想拿了宝藏赶紧走人。
I just want to get the treasure and get out of here,
[Theo] 兄弟。
bro.
[Parrot] 这倒是。
Yeah, that's fair.
[Theo] 这可比咱们预想的麻烦多了，不过倒也确实。
This is, like, way more than we bargained for, but that's kind of true.
[Theo] 大概吧。
I guess.
[Theo] 看来咱是陷进去了，兄弟。
I guess we're in this deep, bro.
[Theo] 不行。
We can't.
[Theo] 我们过不去。
We can't come.
[Theo] 不拿到宝藏我们绝不回头。
We can't come back without the treasure.
[Parrot] 我和Theo在藏身处干等了好几个钟头，
Theo and I spent the next few hours waiting around in our hideout,
[Parrot] 直到我确信时间已经过去很久很久。
until eventually I was confident that more than enough time had passed.
[Parrot] Theo？
Theo?
[Parrot] 西奥。
Theo.
[Parrot] 时间够久了。
It's been more than enough time.
[Parrot] 走起。
Let's go.
[Parrot] 拿上装备。
Let's grab our stuff.
[Parrot] 没错，百分百。
Yeah, 100%.
[Parrot] 好，出发。
Okay, let's go.
[Parrot] 你在哪？
Where are you?
[Theo] 我要留着我的图腾。
I'm gonna keep my totem on.
[Parrot] 她不在这儿。
She's not here.
[Theo] 你确定？
You sure?
[Theo] 她可能躲起来了。
She could be like hiding.
[Parrot] 兄弟，都过去好几天了。
Dude, it's been days.
[Theo] 说不好。
I don't know.
[Theo] 她不像没耐心的人。
She doesn't strike me as the impatient type.
[Parrot] 准备好了吗？
You ready?
[Parrot] 嗯。
Yeah.
[Parrot] 快跟上。
Come on.
[Parrot] 快告诉我那就是钥匙。
Please tell me that was the key.
[Parrot] 哎呀。
Oh, my.
[Theo] 我的天。
Oh, my God.
[Parrot] 上。
Go.
[Theo] 快上快上快上。
Go, go, go, go.
[Parrot] 我们进去吧。
Let's go in.
[Theo] 我的天。
Oh, my God.
[Parrot] 这是什么？
What is this?
[Parrot] 这是啥？
[Theo] 这——搞什——哇！
It's a- what the- Whoa!
[Theo] 我的天！
Oh my God!
[Theo] 哟！
Yo!
[Parrot] 我的天。
Oh my God.
[Parrot] 就是这里。
This is it.
[Theo] 就是这儿。
[Theo] 哇，我们马上要看到黑手党陵墓了！
Oh, dude, we're about to see the Tomb of the Mafia!
[Theo] 嘿，
Yo,
[Theo] 我穿好盔甲了。
I'm putting on my armor.
[Parrot] 我不。
I don't.
[Theo] 不知道会看到什么。
I don't know what we're about to see.
[Parrot] 我觉得这玩意儿有戏。
I think this is something.
[Parrot] 搞什么。
What the.
[Theo] 我有点紧张，兄弟。
I'm nervous, dude.
[Parrot] 这是啥？
What am I looking at?
What is this?
[Parrot] 说不好。
I don't know.
[Theo] 怎么了。
What's.
[Theo] 这波怎么打？
What's the play here?
[Theo] 走起，兄弟。
Let's go, dude.
[Parrot] 这像个迷宫。
This looks like it's some sort of maze.
[Theo] 可能有陷阱。
I think there could be traps.
[Parrot] 说不好。
I don't know.
[Parrot] 哥们，这。
Dude, like.
[Theo] 好，左边墙。
All right, left wall.
[Theo] 哥们，这什么情况？
Dude, what is going on?
[Parrot] 看来这是条死路。
This looks like a dead end.
[Parrot] 我以为坟墓就在那扇门后面。
I thought the tomb was supposed to be behind that door.
[Theo] 不好说。
I don't know, man.
[Theo] 我。
I'm.
[Theo] 我有点慌了。
I'm getting freaked out.
[Theo] 这也太离谱了。
This is, like, ridiculous.
[Parrot] 哇 搞什么
Dude, what the.
[Theo] 这走廊真长。
This hallway is so long.
[Parrot] 没完没了了。
It just keeps going and going.
[Parrot] 这像是个护墓迷宫。
I think it's some sort of maze created to protect the tomb.
[Parrot] 他们好像故意让人在这儿迷路似的。
Like they're expecting that people get lost in here.
[Theo] 怎么咱们啥都没撞见呢？
How come we haven't like run into anything though?
[Theo] 那应该放点陷阱什么的。
There should be like traps or something then.
[Parrot] Theo？
Theo?
[Theo] 哦。
Oh.
[Theo] 我的天。
Oh my god.
[Theo] 在哪儿？
Where?
[Theo] 我看不见。
I can't see.
[Parrot] 她来了。
She's here.
[Theo] 你带图腾了吧？
You have your totem, right?
[Parrot] 怎么办？
What do we do?
[Theo] 这是。
What is.
[Theo] 好的，鹦鹉。
Okay, parrot.
[Theo] 快跑。
Just run.
[Theo] 快跑，鹦鹉。
Just run, parrot.
[Theo] 快跑。
Just run.
[Parrot] 你没事吧？
Yo, are you gonna be fine?
[Theo] 嗯，我会的。
Yeah, I'll.
[Theo] 我会尽力。
I'll do my best.
[Theo] 你连盔甲都没穿，兄弟。
You have no armor, bro.
[Theo] 快走。
Just go.
[Parrot] 西奥。
Theo.
[Parrot] 喂？
Hello?
[Parrot] 哥们，他说过自己没事的。
Dude, he told me he was gonna be fine.
[Parrot] 他在说什么？
What is he talking about?
[Parrot] 哥们，Theo走了
Dude, with Theo gone,
[Parrot] 我得做个决定。
I had a decision to make.
[Parrot] 一边是回头放弃寻找古墓。
On one hand, I could turn around and stop searching for the tomb.
[Parrot] 但想到西奥可能还在这里头，
But knowing that Theo could potentially still be in here,
[Parrot] 我没得选。
I didn't have a choice.
[Parrot] 我只能继续前进。
I had to keep pushing forward.
[Parrot] 这是啥？
What is this?
[Parrot] 西奥。
Theo.
[Parrot] 这些是Theo的物品。
These are Theo's items.
[Parrot] 她把他干掉了。
She killed him.
[Parrot] 她居然杀了Theo。
She actually killed Theo.
[Parrot] 我那时就明白，再往前走，
By this point, I knew that if I kept going,
[Parrot] 我差点就没了。
I was going to die.
[Parrot] 不过话说回来，要是我现在回头，
But then again, if I turned back now,
[Parrot] 这回我可真是两手空空了。
I would be leaving empty-handed in every single way.
[Parrot] 我必须继续前进。
I had to keep moving.
[Parrot] 这到底是什么？
What even is this?
[Theo] 今天我加入了隐形黑手党。
Today I joined the Invisible Mafia.
[Theo] 我最好的朋友被迫加入了黑手党，从此我再也没见过她。
My best friend was forced to join the Mafia and I haven't seen her since.
[Theo] 那我加入自己，尽量保护队友，
So if I join myself and protect as many members as possible,
[Theo] 我可能也在保护她。
I might be protecting her too.
[Theo] 她在我进服时一直护着我，这是我该做的。
She always protected me when I joined the server, so it's the least I can do.
[Theo] 但愿我不用和玩家动手。
I just hope I won't have to kill any players.
[Theo] 我恨透黑手党了。
I hate the mafia so much.
[Theo] 真希望我们不用再互相躲躲藏藏。
I wish we could all stop being invisible around each other.
[Theo] 或许这样我就能再见她一面。
Maybe then I'd be able to see her again.
[Theo] 黑帮今天被击败了，但我还是隐形的。
The mafia was defeated today, but I'm still invisible.
[Theo] 所有黑手党成员都知道，入伙时必须丢一颗末影珍珠——哪天要是没隐身，它可能就会要了你的命。
Every mafia member knows that when you become a member, you have to throw an ender pearl that might one day kill you if you're ever not invisible.
[Theo] 我最近发现这只是部分真相。
I recently discovered that this is only half of the truth.
[Theo] 黑手党把财宝都藏在这座秘密古墓里了，要是任何物品被带出去，所有成员都会立刻被虚空处决。
The mafia has hidden away all its treasures inside this secret tomb and if any item leaves this place all members will be killed by the void at once.
[Theo] 我不确定还剩多少珍珠，但肯定有几百甚至上千。
I'm not sure how many pearls are left but it has to be hundreds if not thousands.
[Theo] 我不敢数它们有多少。
I'm too afraid to count all of them.
[Theo] 我会不惜一切代价守护这里的宝藏。
I'll spend the rest of my time on this server protecting the treasure at all costs.
[Theo] 我来扮怪物，把玩家都吓跑。
I'll pretend to be a monster so that all players will run far away from this place.
[Theo] 希望前黑手党成员能安稳过日子。
I hope the former mafia members can live peacefully.
[Theo] 他们永远不会知道我的付出，但这不重要。
They'll never know what I'm doing for them, but that doesn't matter.
[Theo] 但愿我朋友还在服务器上。
I just hope my friend is still playing on the server.
[Theo] 真想离开这儿去找她。
I wish I could leave this place and go look for her.
[Parrot] 啥？
What?
[Theo] 今天又有一队寻宝者出现在入口。
Today another group of treasure hunters showed up at the entrance again.
[Theo] 他们没像我希望的那样被警报吓跑。
They didn't run from the alarm as I had hoped.
[Theo] 就算我亮明身份，他们也没在怕的。
Even when I revealed my identity, they weren't scared.
[Theo] 幸好又来了一队人，让我有理由停手了。
Luckily, another group showed up and gave me an excuse to stop killing them.
[Theo] 真希望他们别回来，可他们偷了我的钥匙，还是进了地下墓穴。
I hoped they wouldn't come back, but they entered the catacombs after stealing my key.
[Theo] 我跟一个叫Theobald的打过，但就是下不了手。
I fought one of them named Theobald, but I just couldn't get myself to kill him.
[Theo] 他让我想起了我的老朋友。
He reminded me too much of my old friend.
[Theo] 他舍命保护朋友，就像我进服时我朋友也会保护我一样。
He protected his friend with his life just like my friend would protect me when I joined the server.
[Theo] 我可能让Theobald把物品都放进箱子，然后把他带上来了。
I may have Theobald put all of his items in a chest and brought him up.
[Theo] 我还是不确定这么做对不对。
I'm still not sure if it was the right thing to do.
[Theo] 我曾骗自己说，扮怪物不过是想吓跑旁人，
I used to tell myself that I'm only pretending to be a monster to scare people away,
[Theo] 但最近我开始觉得，自己或许真是个怪物。
but recently I've started to believe that maybe I really am a monster.
[Theo] 但愿有朝一日，读到这本书的人能明白——我根本不想当什么英雄。
I wish that one day someone might read this book and realize that I don't want to be one.
[Parrot] 你？
You?
[Parrot] 你其实从没想过要杀任何人？
You never actually wanted to kill anyone?
[Parrot] 你这么做是为了保护大家。
You were just doing it to protect other people.
[Parrot] 你也没解决掉Theo？
You didn't kill Theo either?
[Parrot] 每个都是独立个体。
each one of these is a singular person.
[Parrot] Marlo，你去哪儿？
Marlo, where are you going?
[Parrot] 谁从墓里拿东西，谁就得死。
If someone takes something from the tomb they all die.
[Parrot] 抱歉。
I'm sorry.
[Parrot] 黑手党之墓。
The Tomb of the Mafia.
[Parrot] 就是这儿。
This is it.
[Parrot] 每个房间都装满了完全不同的资源。
Each of these rooms is filled with a completely different resource.
[Parrot] Theo？
Theo?
[Parrot] 西奥？
[Parrot] 等等。
Wait.
[Theo] 你还活着。
You're alive.
[Theo] 等等。
Yeah, wait.
[Theo] 你。
You.
[Theo] 这是我的。
This is my.
[Theo] 你把我的东西拿回来了。
You got my stuff back.
[Theo] 我的天。
Oh, my God.
[Theo] 哥们，啥情况？
Dude, what?
[Theo] 怎么回事？
What even happened?
[Theo] 你拿到旅行物品了吗？
Did you get any of the trip?
[Theo] 你找到墓穴了吗？
Did you find the tomb?
[Theo] 天啊。
Oh, my God.
[Theo] 老兄，都怪我。
Dude, it's all my.
[Theo] 我学舌。
I parrot.
[Theo] 这肯定就像，
This has gotta be like,
[Theo] 我不行了，哥们，真不想干了。
I don't even, I don't want to do this anymore, bro.
[Parrot] 外国人。
Foreign.
[Theo] 那你找到墓室没？
So did you find the tomb or what?
[Theo] 比如？
Like, what?
[Theo] 怎么回事？
What even happened?
[Parrot] 嗯，
Yeah,
[Parrot] 我找到了。
I did find it.
[Theo] 哥们，我居然也漏了这个宝箱。
Dude, I cannot believe I missed this treasure, too.
[Theo] 这也太离谱了。
That's so messed up.
[Theo] 你带了多少？
Like, okay, so how much of it did you bring?
[Theo] 你拿到了多少？
How much of it did you get?
[Theo] 你有肩膀吗？
Like, do you have shoulders on you?
[Parrot] 没，我啥都没拿。
Like, no, I didn't take anything.
[Theo] 什么？
What?
[Theo] 数千万件物品，你却什么都没拿。
Tens of millions of items, and you took nothing.
[Theo] 什么？
What?
[Theo] 你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
[Theo] 喂？
Hello?
[Parrot] 哥们，
Dude,
[Parrot] 我错看她了。
I was wrong about her.
[Theo] 大概。
About.
[Theo] 马洛的事？
About Marlow?
[Theo] 嗯。
Yeah.
[Parrot] 我对其他人都看走了眼。
And I've been wrong about everybody else.
[Parrot] 我知道我有些事总惹你烦。
And, like, I know you get annoyed at me a lot for some of the stuff I do,
[Parrot] 你当然有理由不爽，但我想说，
which, like, you have every right to get annoyed, but I just wanted to say,
[Parrot] 抱歉让你经历这些。
I'm sorry for, like, putting you through all this.
[Theo] 嘿，
Hey,
[Theo] 我的意思是。
I mean.
[Theo] 我原谅你了，哥们。
I forgive you, man.
[Theo] 那我们现在干嘛？
So what are we going to do now?
[Theo] 我们完蛋了。
We're.
[Theo] 咱们又破产了吧？
We're just broke again, right?
[Parrot] 我还没想好。
I don't know yet.
[Parrot] 不过我能肯定地说，我彻底放弃寻宝了。
I can pretty confidently say that I'm done hunting treasure, though.
[Theo] 什么？
What?
[Theo] 我。
I.
[Theo] 我还以为你想拯救服务器呢。
I thought you, like, wanted to save the server.
[Theo] 我们该怎么
How are we gonna.
[Theo] 没有乐魂我们怎么行动？
How are we gonna do anything without.
[Parrot] 说实话，就那些东西呗。
Like, stuff, to be honest?
[Parrot] 我彻底懵了。
I don't even know anymore.
[Parrot] 我都不知道想干嘛。
Like, I don't even know what I want to do.
[Parrot] 等我找到方法，你愿意跟我走吗？
But when I figure that out, will you come with me?
[Theo] 嗯，那必须的。
Yeah, I mean, dude, of course.
[Parrot] 你
You're.
[Theo] 你是我最好的朋友，对吧？
You're my best friend, right?
[Theo] 再说了，哥们，要是我不跟你一起，你一天都活不过。
Plus, dude, if I didn't come with you, you'd be dead within a day.
[Parrot] 好嘞。
Okay, dude.
[Parrot] 行。
All right, bro.
[Parrot] 好，我们随便说点啥。
All right, we're saying anything.
[Theo] 你说我不对。
Tell me I'm wrong.
[Theo] 你倒是说说我哪儿不对。
[Parrot] 我才是最大的鸟，兄弟，兄弟。
I'm the biggest bird, bro, bro.
[Theo] 你可不是最大的鸟。
You are not the biggest bird.
[Theo] 你这就纯属胡扯了，兄弟。
That is just objectively false, bro.
[Theo] 说真的，这机器要是没我肯定飞得更快。
I'm like, honestly, this machine would fly a lot faster if I wasn't here.
[Theo] 我就是这么沉。
I'm just that heavy.